how's it going everyone 10-5 here with a
very very special deal today before I
start things up I would like to wish all
of you a happy new year whoa yeah
[ __ ] hope you guys are having fun
this 2016 because I don't know I'm I'm
hanging out all my friends saw mac Sonja
knockers Bob y'all all that good [ __ ] so
I thought it would be a really awesome
idea for the first video of the new year
to be a very very sexy one because it is
gonna blow your mind for that further
dude this is the top five Sonic
Underground fanservice moments I was
watching sock on the ground episode 10
come out where you I sectors just like
bobbing some [ __ ] like Sonic right there
with like a leaf blowing [ __ ] I shake I
don't know why it doesn't even matter
how hard you try
as you can see right there but Sonic was
like blowing the leaves I Bobby's on it
he turn around shop I was elite blowing
Bobby's clothes almost just came came
right off like I couldn't believe that
[ __ ] it was so [ __ ] sexy oh my God
look at that bob is closed they just
come right off
oh they sexy and [ __ ] it all there we
go that's a good one when you were
pajama you're basically naked butt naked
hey I don't know why it doesn't even
matter how harsh try time to move on to
number four number four is well I don't
only gotta say this [ __ ] it's [ __ ]
Mindy I mean damn as you can see like
the [ __ ] singing it [ __ ] but you know
that's not sexy but what is sexy let me
just skip ahead and [ __ ] there's like a
really gets enough a bud right here look
at that ass oh my God I couldn't believe
that [ __ ] I thought I thought something
was up why was why did she have an ass
and I found out why if you go to the
French version look at this [ __ ] look at
that this is a [ __ ] this is not even
edited oh my God yeah it's Susan on her
ass I can look at that that is unedited
she's got big bud look at that [ __ ] oh
my God hey I don't know why it doesn't
even matter how hard she tried number
three this is a good one look at every
one that you saw that jogger that that
is that's a cool kid as you can see like
would dress up in like [ __ ] I don't know
anybody oh here's the good pop Sonic he
little like he is taking it all off look
that boom oh my God look at that [ __ ] he
is like he's basically doing a
striptease he's basically taking off his
clothes I couldn't believe this I really
could not I'm liking I poop my pants cuz
I thought he was doing a striptease no
job I thought Bobby was around the
corner some [ __ ] Sonic saw him so is
taking it off ten arms right yeah look
at that [ __ ]
it's time go to the very next scene its
proper [ __ ] that's right [ __ ] they
knew it was becoming too sexy so they
had to like change I'm collar and [ __ ]
they know that they knew what they were
doing oh my God hey I don't know why it
doesn't even matter how harsh try on the
two as you can see with office you don't
let me tell on the sandwich here they
make that nice and lab for you [ __ ]
look at that look at that he goes
outside he sees not as a [ __ ] baby
son he sucks sees he sees that ass like
you can check in his butt crack and [ __ ]
oh my God so I knew that look he was
like speeding out that he saw that ass
he took off running like oh my God look
at that bone look at the even had to put
it off screen because he is getting way
too [ __ ] sex today like honest you
cannot believe that it shouldn't it
should have been [ __ ] sense because
let feel it's it's what's the number one
it may it made a child fear for his life
and run at the speed of sound this is
the first time in his life from their
ass hey I don't know why it doesn't even
matter how harsh try this is why me the
[ __ ] video it's smart ass look at
that look at that ass you can see like
[ __ ] shadow where his his butt crack
his but she is and you think that's bad
look at the French version this is the
French version
yeah oh my God like look at those lives
look at those plump ass lips he's got
but shakes I'm Wes his [ __ ] town he
ain't got none in the cannon version not
know where Bob is all up in that ass I
couldn't believe that I'll be all up on
that ass you were two [ __ ] as you can
see clear clear difference you align if
you say you don't see the difference
that's a [ __ ] but you can edit all
you want edit all you want I mean change
faith you have to work but that that
doesn't change the facts that's a
[ __ ] bud